{
    "subject": "resource/Oconee_Fall_Line_Technical_College",
    "predicate": "property/state",
    "object": "resource/Georgia_(U.S._state)",
    "human_readable": "Oconee Fall Line Technical College is located in Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9379889965057373,
            "question": "Where is Oconee Fall Line Technical College located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.893868088722229,
            "question": "In what state is Oconee Fall Line Technical College situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.754548192024231,
            "question": "What type of institution is Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6316645741462708,
            "question": "What is the history of Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6025819182395935,
            "question": "What are some student clubs or organizations at Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5585782527923584,
            "question": "Can you name any programs offered at Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5474539399147034,
            "question": "What are the admission requirements for Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.522625744342804,
            "question": "How large is the student body at Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49695155024528503,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4562515318393707,
            "question": "Does Oconee Fall Line Technical College offer online courses?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Oconee Fall Line Technical College is located in Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2797_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable alumni from Oconee Fall Line Technical College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2797_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How large is the student body at Oconee Fall Line Technical College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2797_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the admission requirements for Oconee Fall Line Technical College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2797_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2797_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2797/re-ranker-msmarco/67.txt, Oconee Fall Line Technical College (OFTC) is located in Sandersville, Georgia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple mentions that Oconee Fall Line Technical College is located in Sandersville, GA, which is indeed in the state of Georgia. Therefore, the statement \"Oconee Fall Line Technical College is located in Georgia\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}